Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
A SHOP FOR KILLERS
EPISODE 2
JEONG JINMAN. JEONG JINMAN. JEONG JINMAN
Are you
out of your freaking mind?
Mom passed away so suddenly.
There's something strange about it.
I think
we should do an autopsy.
An autopsy?
Jinman.
Mom had surgery
for biliary tract cancer twice.
She suffered for over five years.
The doctor even told us
to prepare for the worst.
She regained energy briefly
because her son she thought was dead
came back after eight years.
Her death wasn't sudden.
Are you sure?
What if I'm not?
What?
Do you want to play
a loving son or something now?
Do you want the whole neighborhood to know
you two don't get along?
Why are you yelling?
There's no time for this.
We have a lot to do.
Jeong Jian!
I told you to stay still!
Oh. no. What do we do?
Come here.
-Jinman.
-Yes?
We'll take care of the preparations here.
Why don't you go home with Jian?
Jian is of no help here.
Please attain enlightenment.
Your mother worried so much about her sons
when she was alive.
It must be so hard for you.
I'm sorry. but who are you?
You don't remember me?
I'm an old friend of Jinman's.
-Oh. I see.
-Yes.
But I don't see Jinman.
Then...
now that Grandma's dead.
we can't see her anymore?
No.
Not anymore.
Dying sucks.
You're right. It sucks.
But...
we all die eventually.
Death isn't something scary.
Do you see that lion?
That lion will die soon.
But take a look.
The lion who's facing death is quiet
while they're all loud.
Why do you think that is?
Only the weak bark.
The strong don't.
You must become strong.
To make your opponent bark.
I'm scared.
Don't be scared.
Whatever makes you scared.
keep your eyes open and face it.
Why aren't you answering it? Isn't it Mom?
Who is it?
How did you get this number?
Listen up. Jian.
I'm going to the funeral hall
to meet Mom and Dad.
You have to stay at home alone.
My friend will come
and ask you to open the door.
But don't just open the door for him.
Give him a riddle.
Open the door only if he solves it.
If he doesn't know the answer.
don't open the door.
Can you do that?
Yes. I can do it.
And I want to give him this riddle.
"What is a horse's favorite sport?"
"Stable tennis."
Jeong Jinman!
Will you be right back?
Yes. I'll be right back.
HAENGUN MANSION
Are you my uncle's friend?
I can't just open the door.
I'll give you a riddle.
I'll open the door if you solve it.
What is a horse's favorite sport?
Solve the riddle.
What is a horse's favorite sport...
Are you really my uncle's friend?
STABLE TENNIS
I'M YOUR UNCLE'S FRIEND. SORRY I'M LATE.
CAN YOU WAIT IN YOUR ROOM FOR A MINUTE?
Fuck. my teeth.
Attain enlightenment. you bastard!
- Are you sure she's in here?
- I saw the door close.
My goodness. I'm so exhausted.
Good grief.
What the hell?
Wow.
Huh?
I can tell.
You're definitely Jeong Jinman's niece.
You'll get seriously hurt
if you fall from there. kid.
You might die or become crippled.
So stop that and come up to me.
Okay? Come on!
No!
Goodness. The apple doesn't fall
far from the tree.
Oh. my goodness!
I think we're in a bit of a jam.
So she's the daughter of the couple
murdered at Boram Funeral Home?
That's right.
Her parents didn't return home
after what happened at the funeral.
so she left to go find them by herself
and got into an accident.
Goodness.
Then what happens to her now?
Well...
She has an uncle.
-Yes.
-But he's been missing for years.
And his social security number
was canceled last year.
JEONG JIAN
INSTRUCTIONS FOR MORGUE USE
RESTRICTED AREA
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
MORGUE
I think I found her.
I'll take care of her and bring her out.
Stand by.
Mommy?
What are you doing here?
I told you to stand by.
Close your eyes. Jian.
Let's go home now.
ONE MONTH LATER
Get out.
Listen up. Jian.
I'm not your parent.
And I can never be.
Which means
I can't do the things
your parents did for you.
It appears to be aphasia
coupled with dissociative amnesia.
It doesn't seem to be a physical problem.
She lost both of her parents.
I think the resulting shock
and post-traumatic stress caused it.
Let's see what happens
with medication and counseling.
There's no big problem with her studies.
but since Jian can't speak.
it's causing some difficulties.
She's stupid.
She still can't say anything.
Hey. can you really not speak?
- She's always like that.
- She's a mute.
- What's he doing?
- Wow.
- Does he like her?
- Jeongmin. what's your deal?
- Out of the blue?
- Are they fighting?
Are you okay?
Did you know?
- What?
- What is it?
That dummy's mom
was stabbed to death by her dad.
- Why?
- What?
- She was having an affair.
Her dad jumped off the roof
of the funeral home and killed himself.
- Really? Suicide?
- Ask your mom.
Everyone in Yecheong knows.
That's crazy!
- Hey. are you okay!
- Hey!
- Are you okay?
- Oh. no.
She can't seem to blend in
with the other kids.
I can see she's an outsider.
Dad!
Mom!
Why are you so late? I'm soaked!
Jiyun. did you have fun today?
Wait for me!
Hey! Wait up!
Hey. Shinae! Let's go together.
Mom!
YECHEONG ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
Hey! Wait up!
You're treating Jian for aphasia. right?
PROTRACTOR
5.000 WON
CLAY
10.000 WON
RECORDER
20.000 WON
TRIANGLE
30.000 WON
CASTANETS
40.000 WON
I understand
what you're trying to say.
However...
I think this problem
is something Jian must overcome
on her own.
It's the crazy mute's fault.
So unlucky.
Yeah.
Hey. shut it.
Let's go.
Jeong...
Jin...
man...
Jeong Jinman!
Why did you come so late?
You said you'd be right back!
Why did you come so late? Why?
I'm sorry I'm late.
Jeong Jian.
Come here.
Let's eat together.
This pork belly's good.
Your front door was open. so I came in.
If it's all right with you.
can I wait for him inside?
My uncle said he wasn't coming home today.
So you should just go back.
I'll tell my uncle
to call you later.
You're the niece
that attends
Gongju National University. right?
Your uncle bragged
about how pretty and smart you are.
I'm not smart or pretty.
I don't attend
Gongju National University. either.
My uncle would never say that.
Do you really know my uncle?
I understand.
I'll call your uncle
and come back next time.
DON'T LET ANYONE ELSE KILL YOU
I'LL COME AND KILL YOU MYSELF. JIAN.
Jian.
Come and look at this.
I hacked into the operator's account
for murthehelp and had a look.
This website is operated
for authorized members only.
Look.
Members can get codes
according to their grades.
The process is a little tricky.
but it says that only those
who pass this can get codes.
Codes?
"Only authorized members with the operator's
codes can purchase items on murthehelp."
"Not all items are available for purchase
with provided codes."
"Each code has a different quality."
"You can only purchase
the qualified items for that code."
A different quality for each code?
Yes.
There are four codes.
People who kill people are Code Red.
I think it's like contract killers
that we see in movies.
Guns. weapons. bombs. and poisons.
It seems they can buy
items needed to kill people.
Spies are Code Purple.
"A code for people
who buy and sell information."
"A variety of listening devices
or cameras."
"Simple weapons or goods that you can use
to kill yourself
when your cover is blown."
It sounds so scary.
Do you want to try it?
Code Yellow is for the clean-up crew.
"Drugs. detergents. and cleaning tools
needed for body disposal and clean-up."
It also says that they provide various
administrative services to evade the law.
You said there are four codes.
What's the last one?
Code Green.
Green?
Yes. but unlike the other codes.
I don't think it has a category.
Code Green.
"Those who have received codes from
murthehelp may never attack Code Green."
"If someone disobeys this
and attacks Code Green.
everyone with a code must risk
their lives to protect Code Green."
So who's Code Green?
The operator of murthehelp.
Your uncle. Jeong Jinman.
And...
code green: JEONG JINMAN. JEONG JIAN
Jeong Jian.
What on earth...
Am I supposed
to believe all this?
Jeongmin.
Does this make sense...
What is this?
What is happening?
What... the heck is that?
I'm not getting any signal.
Darn it!
Jeongmin.
Let's use the back door!
What's with the door?
Is it bulletproof?
What?
Why aren't they moving?
Are they out of bullets?
What's that?
Jeongmin. this way!
Jeongmin!
Shut the door!
Jeongmin. duck!
A SHOP FOR KILLERS
Hello.
Oh. really?
You got married? Congrats!
- Oh. congratulations!
- Thanks.
But does your wife know you do this work?
No way. That would be bad.
By the way.
where were you from again? 707?
No. the UDT/SEAL.
UDT? Really?
Mr. Kim. you're here!
Hello!
-Welcome!
-Hello!
You're here as well.
Yes. sir.
Is married life fun?
Not at all.
Sir. do we have to do that?
After today. it doesn't matter
if we have one or not anyway.
You do what's comfortable for you.
I don't need this code anymore.
Wow!
The veteran warriors have all gathered!
Victory!
-Victory!
You came. Mr. Kim.
Seongjo. has it been a year?
Thank you for changing your mind.
I bet we'll finish early today
if we follow Mr. Kim's lead.
Let's grab some galbi and makgeolli after!
- Sounds good!
- Sure!
What weapons did you bring?
Bring out your babies. Come on.
This is so worn out.
Wow. man!
Where did you get the rail?
Jinman installed it for me. I feel so bad.
I bought this from Jinman too.
Four mags will be enough. right?
By the way. what's up with your gun?
I've used every gun out there.
but this is light and comfortable.
Right. good for you.
I feel kind of bad for Jinman.
Fuck that. He's dead. and we're alive.
We must go on.
All right.
The person who captures the niece
or kills her
will get a fat bonus too.
Everyone! Let's get going.
We'll need to take a piss
and have some snacks on the way.
We should leave now
if we want to make it in time.
He's the one who wasted time
by taking a shit.
Shut your mouth
and go start the car. punk.
All right. Let's go now! Chop-chop!
Let's go!
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today